Finding Aid for the Chancellor's Office Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- National Movement for the Student Vote (National Advisory Board Member) 1972 (Box 0257, Folder 23)
- National Movement for the Student Vote (National Advisory Board Member) 1971-72 (Box 0257, Folder 24)
- Newcomers's Reception 1/20/77 (Box 0257, Folder 25)
- North Carolina Conference for Social Service April 21, 1969-71 (Box 0258, Folder 1)
- North Carolina Conference for Social Service 1963-69 (Box 0258, Folder 2)
- North Carolina, University of -- Department of Political Science: UNC Department of Political Science (file sent 7/19/63) (Box 0258, Folder 3)
- North Carolina, University of -- Department of Political Science (Box 0258, Folder 4)
- North Carolina, University of 12/1962-2/1963 (Box 0258, Folder 5)
- Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company 1978-79 (Box 0258, Folder 6)
- Nutrition Foundation 1978-79 (Box 0258, Folder 7)
- Nutrition Foundation 1977 (Box 0258, Folder 8)
- Nutrition Foundation 1976 (Box 0258, Folder 9)
- Oceanography Materials 1967- (Box 0258, Folder 10)
- Offers/Columbia University Correspondence with interested people A-G 1969 (Box 0258, Folder 11)
- Offers/Columbia University Correspondence with interested people H-N 1969 (Box 0258, Folder 12)
- Offers/Columbia University Correspondence with interested people O-Z 1969 (Box 0259, Folder 1)
- Parker, John A., Recognition Banquet and Gala 4/20/1974 (Box 0259, Folder 2)
- Picnics for Students (Freshmen and Foreign Student) 1974 (Box 0259, Folder 3)
- Picnics for Students (International Students, Senior Class, and Freshman Class) 1973 (Box 0259, Folder 4)
- Picnics, Student 1972 (Box 0259, Folder 5)
- Picnics, Student 1970-71 (Box 0259, Folder 6)
- Picnics, Student 1969 (Box 0259, Folder 7)
- Picnics, Student 1967-68 (Box 0259, Folder 8)
- Picnics, Student 1965-66 (Box 0259, Folder 9)
- Population Crisis Committee 1970-73 (Box 0259, Folder 10)
- Population Crisis Committee 6/1966-69 (Box 0259, Folder 11)
- Portrait 1976 (Box 0259, Folder 12)
- Reference, Letters of 1980 (Box 0259, Folder 13)
- Reference, Letters of 1979 (Box 0259, Folder 14)
- Reference, Letters of A-L 1978 (Box 0259, Folder 15)
- Reference, Letters of M-Z 1978 (Box 0260, Folder 1)
- Reference, Letters of 1977 (Box 0260, Folder 2)
- Reference, Letters of 1976 (Box 0260, Folder 3)
- Reference, Letters of 1975 (Box 0260, Folder 4)
- Reference, Letter of 1974 (Box 0260, Folder 5)
- Reference, Letters of 1973 (Box 0260, Folder 6)
- Reference, Letters of 1972 (Box 0260, Folder 7)
- Reference, Letters of 1971 (Box 0260, Folder 8)
- Reference, Letters of 1970 (Box 0260, Folder 9)
- Reference, Letters of July 1, 1963-69 (Box 0260, Folder 10)
- Raggio, Mrs. Grier H. ("Tex") 1973- (Box 0260, Folder 11)
- Reading is Fundamental 1972-74 (Box 0260, Folder 12)
- Reading is Fundamental 1971 (Box 0260, Folder 13)
- Reading is Fundamental Advisory Board 1970- (Box 0260, Folder 14)
- Rochester, University of 1980 (Box 0260, Folder 15)
- Rockefeller University Council 1978-79 (Box 0260, Folder 16)
- Rockefeller University Council 1977 (Box 0260, Folder 17)
- Round Table 1975-76 (Box 0260, Folder 18)
- Round Table 1972-74 (Box 0260, Folder 19)
- Round Table 1970-71 (Box 0260, Folder 20)
- Round Table 1969 (Box 0260, Folder 21)
- Round Table 1963-68: Round Table Thursday, Feb. 2, 1967 6:30 p.m. Walnut Room, Peabody Student Center (Box 0261, Folder 1)
- Round Table 1963-68 (Box 0261, Folder 2)
- Saint Andrew's School 1980 (Box 0261, Folder 3)
- State Legislatures in American Politics clippings 1966 (Box 0261, Folder 4)
- SALT II 1979 (Box 0261, Folder 5)
- SALT II Seminar Feb. 1, 1979 (Box 0261, Folder 6)
- SALT II Seminar Background Material Feb. 1, 1979 (Box 0261, Folder 7)
- Security Clearance 1964- (Box 0261, Folder 8)
- Smith, McNeill -- Grenville Clark Prize Nomination 1973-75 (Box 0261, Folder 9)
- Smith, McNeill April 25, 1968-72 (Box 0261, Folder 10)
- Southern Academy of Letters, Arts and Science, Inc. 1973 (Box 0261, Folder 11)
- Southern Center for International Studies 1978 (Box 0261, Folder 12)
- Southern Regional Council--Task Force on Southern Rural Development 1978 (Box 0261, Folder 13)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development, Correspondence 1974-76: TFSRD (Box 0261, Folder 14)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development, Correspondence 1974-76: Responses to draft report (Box 0261, Folder 15)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development, Correspondence 1974-76: TFSRD - Atlanta 5/13/1976 (Box 0261, Folder 16)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development, Correspondence 1974-76 (Box 0261, Folder 17)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development (Box 0261, Folder 18)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development (Box 0261, Folder 19)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development (Box 0261, Folder 20)
- Southern Regional Council Task Force on Southern Rural Development Report (Box 0262, Folder 1)
- State Department -- U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency (see transfer file) (Box 0262, Folder 2)
- State Department -- Appointment Data, Arms Control and Disarmament Agency supporting papers 9/20-21/66 (Box 0262, Folder 3)
- State Department -- Advisory Board on Social Science, est. by Director of U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agy. (Box 0262, Folder 4)
- State Department -- U.S. Control and Disarmament Agency March 11, 1965 (Box 0262, Folder 5)
- State Department -- U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency Committee, Social Science Advisory Board: 3-11-1964 (Box 0262, Folder 6)
- State Department -- U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, Committee Social Science Advisory 1964 (Box 0262, Folder 7)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Sills, Joe B., Jr. 1970- (Box 0262, Folder 8)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Sills, Joe B., Jr. 1966-69 (Box 0262, Folder 9)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Sills, Joe Byrns 1963-65 (Box 0262, Folder 10)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Shrago, Harry 1970 (Box 0262, Folder 11)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Student Research Assistant 1970-74 (Box 0262, Folder 12)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Shrago, Harry 1969- (Box 0262, Folder 13)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69: Halper, Thomas 1966 (Box 0262, Folder 14)
- Student Research Assistant (Fellow) 1963-69 (Box 0262, Folder 15)
- Taft Institute of Government 1973-77 (Box 0262, Folder 16)
- Tanabe, Eru October 10, 1971-74 (Box 0262, Folder 17)
- Transylvania University Bicentennial Celebration Founders' Board 1978- (Box 0262, Folder 18)
- Truman, Harry S. Scholarship Foundation Consultant of the Board 1976- (Box 0262, Folder 19)
- Tulane University 1980- (Box 0262, Folder 20)
- United Nations University, The American Council for 1978-80 (Box 0262, Folder 21)
- United Nations University, The American Council for 1976-77 (Box 0262, Folder 22)
- Vanderbilt/Personal Items (Box 0262, Folder 23)
- Watauga Association (formerly " The Group ") 1972-74 (Box 0262, Folder 24)
- White House Assignment 1971 (Box 0262, Folder 25)
- White House Fellows 1970-72 (Box 0262, Folder 26)
- White House Commission on White House Fellows 1969- (Box 0262, Folder 27)
- White House -- President's Task Force on Education 1967 (Box 0262, Folder 28)
- White House--Meetings of President's Task Force on Education 1966-67: Third Meeting 2/11/67 (Box 0263, Folder 1)
- White House--Meetings of President's Task Force on Education 1966-67: Second Meeting 1/13-14/67 (Box 0263, Folder 2)
- White House--Meetings of President's Task Force on Education 1966-67: First Meeting 11/22/66 (Box 0263, Folder 3)
- White House--Meetings of President's Task Force on Education 1966-67 (Box 0263, Folder 4)
- White House--Task Force on Priorities in Higher Education 1969: White House (personal) 1970-74 (Box 0263, Folder 5)
- White House--Task Force on Priorities in Higher Education 1969 (Box 0263, Folder 6)
- Heard, Mrs. Alexander (Jean) 1973-76 (Box 0263, Folder 7)
- American Council on Education--National Panel for the National Identification Program 1977 (Box 0263, Folder 8)
- Aspen Institute for Humanities Studies 1978-79 (Box 0263, Folder 9)
- Association of American Universities--Athletics 1972 (Box 0263, Folder 10)
- Automobile 1970- (Box 0263, Folder 11)
- University Automobile 1966-69 (Box 0263, Folder 12)
- Books and Articles--Saturday Review, unfinished 1964 (Box 0263, Folder 13)
- Campaign Finance 1976 (Box 0263, Folder 14)
- Campaign Finance 1973-74: Campaign Finance Data needed for 6/19-20 (Box 0263, Folder 15)
- Campaign Finance 1973-74: Citizens Research Foundation 2/27-28 (Box 0263, Folder 16)
- Campaign Finance 1973-74 (Box 0263, Folder 17)
- Campaign Finance 1976-79 (Box 0264, Folder 1)
- Center for Inter-American Relations 1977-79 (Box 0264, Folder 2)
- Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions 1966-69 (Box 0264, Folder 3)
- Century III Commission 1978 (Box 0264, Folder 4)
- Chamber of Commerce -- Cultural Facilities Commission 1969 (Box 0264, Folder 5)
- Christmas Card Project 1981 (Box 0264, Folder 6)
- Christmas Card Project 1980 (Box 0264, Folder 7)
- Christmas Cards 1976: Christmas Card File Working Papers (Box 0264, Folder 8)
- Christmas Cards 1976 (Box 0264, Folder 9)
- Christmas Cards 1975 (Box 0264, Folder 10)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1973 (Box 0264, Folder 11)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1972 (Box 0264, Folder 12)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1971 (Box 0264, Folder 13)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1969 (Box 0264, Folder 14)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1967-68 (Box 0264, Folder 15)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1966 (Box 0264, Folder 16)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73: Christmas Card Project 1965 (Box 0264, Folder 17)
- Christmas Card Project 1965-73 (Box 0264, Folder 18)
- Commission on U.S.--Latin American Relations (Minutes of meetings) 1974 (Box 0264, Folder 19)
- Commission on United States--Latin American Relations--General 1976- (Box 0265, Folder 1)
- Commission on U.S.--Latin American Relations (Reports) 1974 (Box 0265, Folder 2)
- Crook, Clark Harris (Box 0265, Folder 3)
- Expense Data 1966-67 (Box 0265, Folder 4)
- Expense Data 1963-65 (Box 0265, Folder 5)
- Ford Foundation 1969-77 (Box 0265, Folder 6)
- Historic Buildings Commission 1978- (Box 0265, Folder 7)
- Institute of Public Affairs, Inc. 1-27-69 Meeting (Box 0265, Folder 8)
- Institute of Public Affairs 1968-69 (Box 0265, Folder 9)
- Journal of Politics (Box 0265, Folder 10)
- Journal of Politics Volume 26, No. 1 Feb. 1964 Galley Proofs Vol. I (Box 0265, Folder 11)
- Journal of Politics Volume 26, No. 1 Feb. 1964 Galley Proofs Vol. II (Box 0265, Folder 12)
- Meet the Press August 30, 1970 (Box 0265, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 0265, Folder 14)
- National Institute of Public Affairs 1967-69 (Box 0265, Folder 15)
- Residence 1972 (Box 0265, Folder 16)
- Boleyjack, Etta Maid, Chancellor's Residence 1967-70 (Box 0265, Folder 17)
- Residence 1970- (Box 0265, Folder 18)
- Residence 1969 (Box 0265, Folder 19)
- Residence, Addition to the Chancellor's 1965-69 (Box 0266, Folder 1)
- Residence, Chancellor's 1964-68: Swimming Pool at 211 Deer Park Drive 1968 (Box 0266, Folder 2)
- Residence, Chancellor's 1964-68 (Box 0266, Folder 3)
- Budgets 1965-72 (Box 0266, Folder 4)
- B, miscellany (Box 0266, Folder 5)
- Calendar -- July 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 6)
- Calendar -- June 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 7)
- Calendar -- May 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 8)
- Calendar -- April 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 9)
- Calendar -- March 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 10)
- Calendar -- January and February 1982 (Box 0266, Folder 11)
- Calendar -- December 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 12)
- Calendar -- November 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 13)
- Calendar -- October 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 14)
- Calendar -- September 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 15)
- Calendar -- August 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 16)
- Calendar -- July 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 17)
- Calendar -- March, April, May 1981 (Box 0266, Folder 18)
- Calendar 1979-80 (Box 0266, Folder 19)
- Calendar 1974-75 (Box 0266, Folder 20)
- Calendar -- July thru December 1970 (Box 0266, Folder 21)
- Calendar -- January thru June 1970 (Box 0266, Folder 22)
- Carnegie Corporation -- Carnegie Foundation 1975-76 (Box 0266, Folder 23)
- Centennial Celebration 1974 (Box 0266, Folder 24)
- Clark, Blake 1970-77 (Box 0266, Folder 25)
- Coddington, Parker L. 1967-68 (Box 0266, Folder 26)
- College of Arts and Science 1959-69 (Box 0266, Folder 27)
- College of Arts and Science -- Ruml Proposals 1959 (Box 0266, Folder 28)
- Commencement 1980 (Box 0266, Folder 29)
- Commission, Historic Buildings 1973-76 (Box 0267, Folder 1)
- Commission to Review the Freshman Year 1971 (Box 0267, Folder 2)
- Commission on the Status of Women 1977 (Box 0267, Folder 3)
- Committee--Academic Policy (Box 0267, Folder 4)
- ad hoc Advisory Committee 3/1/63 (Box 0267, Folder 5)
- Committee--Administrative Budget 1973-75 (Box 0267, Folder 6)
- Budget Review for Advisory Budget Committee and new long-range planning 1975 (Box 0267, Folder 7)
- Committee--Admission Policies and Size of Schools 1972 (Box 0267, Folder 8)
- Committees--Committee on Athletics 1972-74 (Box 0267, Folder 9)
- Committee--Budget 1970-71 (Box 0267, Folder 10)
- Committee--Calendar 1970-74 (Box 0267, Folder 11)
- Committee on Calendar 1966-70 (Box 0267, Folder 12)
- Committees--Commission on the Status of Women 1977 (Box 0267, Folder 13)
- Committees--Community Affairs Board 1971-73 (Box 0267, Folder 14)
- Committees--Ad Hoc Committee on Composition of the Undergraduate Student Body 1971 (Box 0267, Folder 15)
- Committees--Committee on Continuing Education 1972-77 (Box 0267, Folder 16)
- Committees--External Affairs Council 1970-74 (Box 0267, Folder 17)
- Committees--Council on Human Relations 1969-70 (Box 0267, Folder 18)
- Public Relations, Special Committee to make recommendations for 1961 (Box 0267, Folder 19)
- Committee--Sarratt Monitoring 1972 (Box 0267, Folder 20)
- Student Needs, Committee to Evaluate 1963 (Box 0267, Folder 21)
- Committee--University Budget 1970-71 (Box 0267, Folder 22)
- Committees--Vanderbilt Student Communications, Inc. 1976 (Box 0267, Folder 23)
- Doyne Presentation for New Chamber Committee (Box 0267, Folder 24)
- Complaints 1980-81 (Box 0267, Folder 25)
- Complaints 1976 (Box 0267, Folder 26)
- Complaints 1970 (Box 0267, Folder 27)
- Complaint--YSA/Gay Liberation (Dance) 1972-73 (Box 0267, Folder 28)
- Complaints--Student Court Procedures 1965 (Box 0267, Folder 29)
- Complaints 1964 (Box 0267, Folder 30)
- Complaints--Academic Freedom 1963 (Box 0267, Folder 31)
- Complaint--Langford et al 1956 (Box 0268, Folder 1)
- Computer Center 1977 (Box 0268, Folder 2)
- Council on Southern Univeristies 1971 (Box 0268, Folder 3)
- Council on Southern Universities, Report to the March 17, 1975 (Box 0268, Folder 4)
- Crawford, Meredith P. 1940-53 (Box 0268, Folder 5)
- Cummings, Tom 1967 (Box 0268, Folder 6)
- C, Miscellany (Box 0268, Folder 7)
- Danforth Foundation 1968 (Box 0268, Folder 8)
- Davidson, Donald 1968 (Box 0268, Folder 9)
- Davis, Shelby Cullom 1969 (Box 0268, Folder 10)
- Day Files 1976 (Box 0268, Folder 11)
- Denson, John Lane 1966 (Box 0268, Folder 12)
- Development Foundation 1973-74 (Box 0268, Folder 13)
- Development Foundation 1968-69 1972-75 (Box 0268, Folder 14)
- Development Foundation Miscellaneous 1967 (Box 0268, Folder 15)
- Development Office--Miscellaneous 7-12/1966 (Box 0268, Folder 16)
- Development Office--New Fund Drive 7/1965-4/1966 (Box 0268, Folder 17)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Minutes of the National Development Committee 1960-61 (Box 0268, Folder 18)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Miscellaneous 1959-62 (Box 0268, Folder 19)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Motion Picture for fund-raising 1960-62 (Box 0268, Folder 20)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Organization Charts 1960-61 (Box 0268, Folder 21)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Prospects, or sources of money 1960-61 (Box 0268, Folder 22)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Publications (Box 0268, Folder 23)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Publicity 1960-62 (Box 0268, Folder 24)
- Development Foundation--Capital Gifts Campaign-Statiscal Tables and Studies 1960-63 (Box 0268, Folder 25)
- Development Foundation--The Committee on Wills 1958-64 (Box 0268, Folder 26)
- Divinity 1966-70 (Box 0268, Folder 27)
- Dobrin, John 1965-66 (Box 0268, Folder 28)
- Dormitories 1965-73 (Box 0268, Folder 29)
- Drugs 1968-69 (Box 0268, Folder 30)
- Don-Dt Miscellaneous Correspondence 1950-70 (Box 0268, Folder 31)
- Duke University 1970-74 (Box 0269, Folder 1)
- Duke University 1965-69 (Box 0269, Folder 2)
- Duncan, Marvin 1948-52 (Box 0269, Folder 3)
- Du Pont De Nemours 1970-74 (Box 0269, Folder 4)
- Du-Dz Miscellaneous Correspondence 1970-74 (Box 0269, Folder 5)
- Engineering, School of -- Committee of Visitors 1961-68 (Box 0269, Folder 6)
- Facilities, Use of University 1963 (Box 0269, Folder 7)
- Faculty 1968-69 1975 (Box 0269, Folder 8)
- Fields, Emmett 1977-81 (Box 0269, Folder 9)
- Fleming, Partee 1965 (Box 0269, Folder 10)
- Force, William F. 1969-70 (Box 0269, Folder 11)
- Ford Foundation 1969 (Box 0269, Folder 12)
- Fraternities 1967-68 (Box 0269, Folder 13)
- Jamison, Henry D., Jr. 1952-67 (Box 0269, Folder 14)
- Nashville University Center Council 1970 (Box 0269, Folder 15)
- Medicine, School of "Planning for Development" 1973 (Box 0269, Folder 16)
- Veterans Administration 1963-69 (Box 0269, Folder 17)
- Veterans Administration Hospital -- General Hospital, agreements with VUMC and VUH 1944-57 (Box 0269, Folder 18)
- Davidson, Philip G. 1947 (Box 0269, Folder 19)
- Davidson, Philip G. 1944-46 (Box 0269, Folder 20)
- Graduate Faculty 1931-50 (Box 0269, Folder 21)
- Beach, Leonard 1951-52, 1952-53 (Box 0269, Folder 22)
- Graduate Seminar 1949 (Box 0269, Folder 23)
- Davidson, Philip G., Jr. 1950-51 (Box 0269, Folder 24)
- Davidson, Philip G. 1949 (Box 0269, Folder 25)
- Davidson, Philip G. 1948 (Box 0269, Folder 26)
- Beach, Leonard B. 1957-61 (Box 0269, Folder 27)
- Coffman, L. Dale 1945-47 (Box 0269, Folder 28)
- Forrester, William Ray 1951-52 (Box 0269, Folder 29)
- Forrester, William Ray 1949-50 (Box 0269, Folder 30)
- Forrester, William Ray 1949-50 (Box 0269, Folder 31)
- Coffman, L. Dale 1947-49 (Box 0269, Folder 32)
- Beach, Leonard B. 1961-62 (Box 0269, Folder 33)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1945-46 (Box 0269, Folder 34)
- Engineering Camp 1933-36 (Box 0269, Folder 35)
- Engineering Camp Preliminary Plans, Papers, Etc. 1931 (Box 0269, Folder 36)
- Law School (Fund for the Advancement of Education) 1955-57 (Box 0269, Folder 37)
- Dean Lewis, School of Engineering, Division of Research and Development 1952-56 (Box 0269, Folder 38)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1951-53 (Box 0270, Folder 1)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1950-51 (Box 0270, Folder 2)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1947-49 (Box 0270, Folder 3)
- Engineering School Project 1956-57 (Box 0270, Folder 4)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1954-56 (Box 0270, Folder 5)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1957-58 (Box 0270, Folder 6)
- Lewis, Fred J. 1957 (Box 0270, Folder 7)
- Lewis, Fred J. -- School of Engineering Division of Research and Development 1956-57 (Box 0270, Folder 8)
- Engineering, School of (Faculty Changes) 1959-61 (Box 0270, Folder 9)
- Engineering Dean (turned down "feeler" letter, or job) 1959 (Box 0270, Folder 10)
- Engineering Dean 1959 (Box 0270, Folder 11)
- Engineering, School of (Dean Rowe) See transfer file 1961-62 (Box 0270, Folder 12)
- Engineering, School of (Dean Rowe) 1960-61 (Box 0270, Folder 13)
- Engineering, School of (W. H. Rowan, Acting Dean) 1957-60 (Box 0270, Folder 14)
- Zeigler, Frances Helen 1948-49 (Box 0270, Folder 15)
- Zeigler, Frances Helen 1947 (Box 0270, Folder 16)
- Zeigler, Frances Helen 1946 (Box 0270, Folder 17)
- Hereford, Julia 1957-58 (Box 0270, Folder 18)
- Hereford, Julia Nov. 1955-June 30, 1957 (Box 0270, Folder 19)
- Hereford, Julia 1953-55 (Box 0270, Folder 20)
- Hereford, Julia 1951-53 (Box 0270, Folder 21)
- Hereford, Julia 1949-50 (Box 0270, Folder 22)
- Nursing, School of 1959-62 (Box 0270, Folder 23)
- General Electric Company 1964 (Box 0271, Folder 1)
- Goldman, Sachs and Company 1975-77 (Box 0271, Folder 2)
- Goodpasture, Ernest W. 1946-77 (Box 0271, Folder 3)
- Graduate Journal, The (Austin, Texas) 1963-65 (Box 0271, Folder 4)
- Graduate School 1975 (Box 0271, Folder 5)
- Gradaute School 1976-77 (Box 0271, Folder 6)
- Graduate School 1970 (Box 0271, Folder 7)
- Harvard University 1968 (Box 0271, Folder 8)
- Hearne, Mary Elizabeth 1978 (Box 0271, Folder 9)
- Hobbs, Nicholas 1967-73 (Box 0271, Folder 10)
- Holladay, Wendell 1969-71 (Box 0271, Folder 11)
- Hustler 1967-69 (Box 0271, Folder 12)
- H, Miscellaneous 1966-68 (Box 0271, Folder 13)
- IIE-Conference on Higher Education in the American Republics Meeting 2-3/67 (Box 0271, Folder 14)
- Impact 1967 (Box 0271, Folder 15)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies - Reynold E. Carlson 1950-53 (Box 0271, Folder 16)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies - Application to Ford Foundation 1951-52 (Box 0271, Folder 17)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies 1947-52 (Box 0271, Folder 18)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies 1947-48 (Box 0271, Folder 19)
- Brazilian Institute 1949-51 (Box 0271, Folder 20)
- Brazilian Studies, Institute of 1959 (Box 0271, Folder 21)
- Brazil - Possible Business Connections 1947-51 (Box 0271, Folder 22)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies, The Establishment of (Box 0271, Folder 23)
- Brazilian Institute - President Dutra's Visit 1949-50 (Box 0271, Folder 24)
- Institute for Brazilian Studies (orginally "Latin-American Institute) 1946-47 (Box 0271, Folder 25)
- Kahn Trust Foundation, Henry M. and Lena Meyer (Abe D. Waldauer, Trustee) 1949-53 (Box 0271, Folder 26)
- Institute for Services to Education 1967 (Box 0271, Folder 27)
- Latin-American Center and Mendonca 1970-71 (Box 0271, Folder 28)
- Law School 1967-71 (Box 0271, Folder 29)
- Law School -- Committee of Visitors 1970 (Box 0271, Folder 30)
- Libraries, Joint University - Vanderbilt Library Excellence Fund (VLEF) 1971-72 (Box 0271, Folder 31)
- Collection Policy of the Joint University Libraries 1975 (Box 0271, Folder 32)
- Long-Range Planning Study 1964 (Box 0271, Folder 33)
- MACE, University's 1967-68 (Box 0271, Folder 34)
- Macy Foundation, Josiah, Jr. 1975-77 (Box 0271, Folder 35)
- Management, Graduate School of, Documentation for a (Box 0271, Folder 36)
- Massey, Richard W., Jr. 1958-62 (Box 0271, Folder 37)
- McGaw, Robert 1965-69 (Box 0271, Folder 38)
- Medicine, School of 1963-76 (Box 0271, Folder 39)
- M, Miscellaneous 1966-75 (Box 0271, Folder 40)
- New York University 1965 (Box 0271, Folder 41)
- Nursing, School of 1967-73 (Box 0271, Folder 42)
- N, Miscellaneous 1965-75 (Box 0271, Folder 43)
- Paisios, John P. March 27, 1970-74 (Box 0271, Folder 44)
- Report of Study of Closer Cooperation between Peabody and Vanderbilt May 1962 (Box 0271, Folder 45)
- Parmer, Educational Trust, Walter O. 1970-79 (Box 0271, Folder 46)
- Payne, Thomas 1975-78 (Box 0271, Folder 47)
- Plough, Abe 1975 (Box 0271, Folder 48)
- President of the University 1977 (Box 0271, Folder 49)
- Pruitt, George -- Blueprint for Leadership - The American College Presidency 1976 (Box 0271, Folder 50)
- Reference 1969 (Box 0271, Folder 51)
- Rand Hall 1965-67 (Box 0271, Folder 52)
- Ravenel, Emily G. 1974 (Box 0271, Folder 53)
- Religion, School of 1954 (Box 0271, Folder 54)
- Requisitions -- Entertainment Expenses Summaries 1967-68, 1970-77 (Box 0272, Folder 1)
- Robins, James A. Died Tuesday Sept. 29, 1959 (Box 0272, Folder 2)
- ROTC 1969 (Box 0272, Folder 3)